# DAVID **DIKE**

17 Brown's Court, Charlottetown · 902-388-5748 daviddike679@gmail.com

I am a creative and highly motivated student who brings forth an independent work spirit as well as the ability to work well with others with a drive for providing excellent service and achieving all stocking needs, and an organized and highly efficient individual in project management with a strong attention to detail to help your organization improve profitability and grow my industry experience.

# **EXPERIENCE**

JAN 2020 - MAR 2022

### **SALES PERSON, CLASSIC COLLECTIONS**

- Maintained up-to-date knowledge of all retail promotions.
- Gave constant updates on new products in stock
- Brought forth excellent customer service skills and a commitment to customer satisfaction and giving them
  what's best.

MAR 2022 - DEC 2022

## **SALES MANAGER, CLASSIC COLLECTIONS**

- Maintained up-to-date knowledge of all retail promotions.
- Ensured everything was up to date, booth in quality and quantity

MAY 2023 - SEP 2023

### **RETAIL ATTENDANT, MARTIME FUN GROUP**

- Performed all retail operations properly
- Ensured everything was being used correctly, and without issues

### **AUGUST 2023 - ON-GOING**

## HOME SOLUTIONS AND COMPUTING RETAIL ADVISOR, BEST BUY

- Provided expert guidance and recommendations to customers, tailoring solutions to their unique needs and preferences.
- Delivered consistently exceptional customer service, ensuring every interaction left a positive and lasting impression.
- Performed expert diagnosis and troubleshooting on customer's electronic devices.

**JAN 2023** 

### **GEEK SQUAD, BEST BUY**

- Proper diagnosis of customers laptops, tablets, and printers
- In-home and in-store services for PC's, TV's, furniture, and security systems

# **EDUCATION**

**SEP 2015** 

### HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, BISHOP OKOYE SPIRITAN SECONDARY SCHOOL

- Member of Robotics Club
- Elected as Captain of Soccer Team
- Awarded Most Resilient Student
- Elected as a BOSSS Functionaries in 2016, and 2019

# NOV 2021 NCUK INTERNATIONAL FOUNDATION YEAR DIPLOMA, BROOKSTONE INTERNATIONAL FOUNDATION COLLEGE Received Scholarship for International Students to Bradford University JAN 2023 BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND Currently studying as a Major in Computer Science, with the aim of specializing in Networking and Cloud Computing

# **SKILLS**

- Programming: Java, Python, Dart, React, HTML, CSS, C++, C#
- Git and GitHub
- Proficiency in use of Microsoft Office
- Leadership Skills
- Highly responsible and reliable
- Highly organized and efficient
- Excellent Customer Service Skills
- Creative Thinking
- Analytical Thinking

# **ACTIVITIES**

- In love with technology and it's accessories
- Playing Soccer
- Playing Basketball
- Swimming
- Playing Volleyball
- Reading Books

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- CISCO NETWORKING
- UDEMY WEB DEVELOPMENT

# **PROJECTS**

GitHub Repository